Buona sera, Luigi's Pizza.
Buona sera.
(Sheldon:)It means good evening
in Italian.
(Sheldon:)May I say, having to explain
that to you calls into question
the authenticity
of your ristorante?
(Leonard:)Okay, I'm out of here.
Un momento.
(Sheldon:)Oh, for heaven's sake.
(Sheldon:)Now you're being
deliberately stupid.
(Sheldon:)Where are you going?
(Leonard:)I'm having dinner
with Priya at Raj's.
(Leonard:)I think Howard's going to be
there. You want to join us?
(Sheldon:)But tonight's Thursday.
(Sheldon:)On Thursdays, everybody
comes over here
(Sheldon:)and has pizza.
(Sheldon:)Or a reasonable facsimile
(Sheldon:)prepared by someone claiming
to be Luigi,
(Sheldon:)but who sounds suspiciously
like Jackie Chan.
(Leonard:)Can't we make a one-time
exception for tonight?
(Sheldon:)We could.
(Sheldon:)We could also
stop using the letter "M,"
but I think that idea is
isguided and oronic.
(Leonard:)Just come with me to Raj's.
(Sheldon:)Well, I don't want
to go to a party.
(Leonard:)It's not a party.
It's the same group of people
(Leonard:)who hang out here
hanging out over there.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, but five people
eating and chatting is a party.